// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let itc = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the built-in permanent memory in a computer called ?",
    answer: "ROM",
    options: [
      "ROM",
      "RAM",
      "CD-ROM",
      "CPU"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The lowest form of computer language is called ?",
    answer: "Machine Language",
    options: [
      "BASIC",
      "FORTRAN",
      "Machine Language",
      "COBOL"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not an output device ?",
    answer: "Mouse",
    options: [
      "Speaker",
      "Printer",
      "Monitor",
      "Mouse"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which one of the following is the brain of computer ?",
    answer: "CPU",
    options: [
      "CPU",
      "Circuit board",
      "ALU",
      "Memory"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A collection of 8 bit is called……… ?",
    answer: "Byte",
    options: [
      "Nibble",
      "Byte",
      "Word",
      "Record"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who is known as the father of the modern comuter ?",
    answer: "Charles Babbage",
    options: [
      "John Atanasoff",
      "Herman Hollerith",
      "Blaise Pascal",
      "Charles Babbage"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A worksheet is a ……………………… ?",
    answer: "Combination of rows and columns ",
    options: [
      "Combination of rows and columns ",
      "Collection of workbooks",
      "Processing software",
      "None of these above"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Second generation of computer were manufactured using which technology ?",
    answer: "Transistors",
    options: [
      "Vacuum tube",
      "Transistors",
      "ICs",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Storage of  1kb means the following number of bytes :",
    answer: "1024",
    options: [
      "1000",
      "1042",
      "1012",
      "1024"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is not a computer hardware ?",
    answer: "Assembler",
    options: [
      "Hard disk",
      "Printer",
      "Assembler",
      "CPU"
    ]
  },
];